Fujinuma Satoru,
you are under arrest for murder and
attempted murder resulting from arson.
It's him!
It can't end like this.
I still have unfinished business.
There's still something I have to do.
Hey.
Go back...
I need to go back...
Just one more time...
Please...
I beg of you!
Go back!
I'm glad I mustered up the courage to come.
I'm really...
really glad.
Are you stupid?
Yeah.
Satoru.
Hinazuki.
Hey there!
I got done early, so I came.
Sorry we're late.
Are we interrupting?
Of course not.
Right, Hinazuki?
Right.
I must succeed...
This time, for sure.
Even if I have to do it alone, even if things get ugly,
I can't have any regrets.
I won't get another chance if I fail.
This is the final Revival!
I'm starving.
Why don't we grab a bite?
I'm broke.
Oh, I got some pocket money.
Wanna go for some pancakes? My treat.
Nicely done, Satoru!
Sure!
Yay!
Oh yeah, Satoru.
Did you read that book
I lent you a couple weeks ago?
Huh?
"The Switched Man" by Poe.
Not yet, sorry.
I don't remember that.
How would I remember a book
I borrowed 18 years ago, anyway?
Give it a try once you get home.
It's really interesting.
I'm home.
Welcome back, Satoru.
Gimme a sec. Dinner will be done soon.
What's wrong, Satoru?
Don't just stand there—
Did you get into a fight with Kayo-chan?
Nah. I'm good.
That so?
Well, let's eat.
Sorry, Mom, but could you keep this in mind?
You can actually take a direct train to Ueno.
What're you even talking about?
February 29th, 1988.
The day before Hinazuki becomes the first victim
in the serial kidnapping and murder case.
This makes it my third time living this day.
You've got guts, Satoru-kun!
He said the same thing last time,
but now it's a day early.
I can't be picky about my methods this time.
Kenya.
Uh, I'm sorry, but I think
I lost that book you lent me.
Let's talk out in the hall, Satoru.
You don't have to worry about the book.
It never existed in the first place.
Let me just get this out of the way, Satoru.
Lately, I've been catching glimpses
of a more serious side to you.
And that makes me happy.
Before, you pretended to care about others
despite having no interest in them, right?
I'm sure you did your best with that, too...
But I like you better as you are now.
However, there's a question that's eating
away at me that I still want answered.
Satoru...
Who are you?
It feels to me like you've become a different person,
or rather, like there's another personality mixed in.
I realized you'd changed the day
I saw you staring at Hinazuki in class.
I'd noticed her bruises long ago,
but I couldn't do anything.
That's how I always am.
I take a step back when dealing with people.
But right in front of me,
you dug deep and got closer to her.
To me, it felt like something had taken control
of you to rebuke me and show me how it's done.
Satoru, just what are you?
I...
I'm...
I am...
A superhero.
Rather, I want to be.
Yeah, you're Satoru, all right.
Kenya, Hinazuki's going to be murdered.
I saw where she's physically abused.
Next time, I'll put an end to it for sure.
Satoru.
You don't become a superhero
after achieving results.
You already are one.
Let me help you.
I wanna be one too.
A superhero.
I always thought you hated Hinazuki.
Like how people dislike others similar to themselves.
Yeah, I did hate her, but at the same time,
I was attracted to something about her.
Oh, I kinda get what you mean.
Satoru, Kenya.
Stand in the hallway with those buckets.
Superheroes often end up with
the short end of the stick, huh?
Tell me about it.
I need to stop by somewhere.
Hiromi, Kenya. Could you take Hinazuki
to the kids' center and wait for me there?
Sure.
Okay.
I can get through tomorrow, March 1st,
if I don't leave Hinazuki alone in the park.
The problem is March 2nd,
the day of our birthday party.
Yuuki-san needs an alibi.
Hey, is your father's room on the ground floor?
Y-Yeah. It's at the corner facing the main street.
Why do you ask?
Oh, I was just wondering if it was noisy at night.
N-Not really, no.
All right. One more thing...
Yuuki-san, do you ever see Hinazuki Kayo?
Wh-Why?
She's been hanging out with our group lately.
R-Really?
No wonder I haven't seen her around for several days.
Way to go, Kayo-chan!
That's darned great for her!
That's the first time I've ever
heard Yuuki-san talk so informally.
L-Laters, Satoru-kun.
Laters.
From how Yuuki-san was acting,
the killer must've seen him and Kayo together
by chance and decided to frame him.
Just you wait, Yuuki-san.
I'm gonna prevent this entire case.
Hinazuki! Kenya!
Hiromi?
Over here!
Sorry, Satoru.
We all decided to come here.
Oh, Satoru! Join us!
I guess you can't play Othello with three people.
I need to be more careful.
I have to avoid radical changes
like these until March 2nd,
or else things could get unpredictable.
I'm home.
One, two...
Satoru! Hinazuki! Happy birthday!
After spending March 1st just like
last time, X-Day is upon me again.
I'm gonna change the future
with my actions from today on.
I forgot something at school.
You're going this late? Do you really need it now?
See ya!
I know it seems unnatural,
but now's not the time to care about that.
This settles it!
Wh-What the hell?
Hey! Who did that?!
Now the police will serve as
Yuuki-san's alibi for tonight.
I'll get rid of her.
If I can keep her away from Hinazuki...
If you would...
just disappear...
Get a hold of yourself, Satoru.
It'd be bad if she died.
What's worse, you could get punished for it,
and then you wouldn't be able to help anyone.
Satoru...
I've been following you for the past two days or so.
Given how desperate you were to save Hinazuki,
I knew you wouldn't think twice
about your own safety.
Thanks, Kenya.
But I really think Hinazuki's in danger today.
You did something rather concerning
before coming here, too.
What was that all about?
Well, that was to call the cops
to that house for a different reason.
I've made up my mind.
I need your help, Kenya.
Let's get the police to stop
Hinazuki's mother from abusing her.
That could cause a big stir, you know.
Good.
Have you thought it through?
I just came up with the idea.
I'll think about the fallout now.
I don't care if it becomes a major incident
or if I get caught midway.
I don't even care if I get punished for it.
No matter what happens,
anything's better than Hinazuki dying.
Just make sure you don't get caught.
It'd make your mom sad.
Nah.
Knowing my mom, she'd be proud of me.
Yeah, I can see that.
Okay, let's do this.
I'm gonna go walk Hinazuki home.
Get going.
We'll clean up here.
I remembered to wear my coat
and gloves when leaving home this time.
Fujinuma...
Hinazuki...
Listen...
I'm gonna kidnap you now. Okay?
Are you stupid?
That I am.
That's why I couldn't think of anything else.
Okay.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Here we are.
A disused school bus.
I hear it was the clubroom for
Izumi Elementary's hockey team.
Hey. So you two came.
Yeah. You sure this is gonna be okay?
Yep.
They got a new bus last year,
so this is just used for storage now.
Let's open the vents before lighting the heater.
It's all rusted.
Try not to make it too obvious.
Okay.
Wow.
Whoa.
This is a pretty cool hideout.
I wouldn't mind living here myself.
Doesn't have a bath, though.
Living in a big house doesn't
always mean you'll be happy.
Even so, I still gotta go home.
Later, Hinazuki.
I need to go home now too,
but I'll be back later in the night.
I'll knock three times, okay?
Thank you, Satoru, Kenya-kun.
No need for thanks.
Just doing what friends do, Kayo-chan.
We'll protect you no matter what, Kayo.
Ow.
"Kayo"? Really?
That was embarrassing for me too.
Besides, you also called her that.
Yeah, it's kinda hard to call her that.
I'll go with "Hina."
You should be the only one to call her "Kayo."
Thanks.
Like I said, no need for thanks.
Besides, the hard part's only just starting, right?
Yeah.
If this ends up becoming public,
act like you know nothing.
Got it.
You sure took your sweet time.
Sorry.
We took a detour and talked about stuff.
Did Hinazuki's mom call by any chance?
Nope. Not a peep.
Oh, right.
I've got an early start tomorrow,
so you don't have to stay up.
I'll make do with this for food.
Come in.
You were up?
I couldn't sleep.
Figures.
Are you hungry?
This is great.
Cup noodles make a good late-night snack, huh?
It's the first time I've had a night like this.
I'd be surprised if you had.
I'm planning a camping trip with Kenya
and the guys for the summer.
You should come.
I don't know if I can...
You can.
Wake up.
It's morning.
Good thing I dropped by.
Let's leave before the Izumi Elementary kids come.
Kayo's late?
This is the lunch broadcast.
Please wash your hands before eating.
Nothing's happened so far.
What do you make of it?
Would Hinazuki's mom have called the police already?
I don't think she'll look for her just yet.
Last time, on March 2nd,
Hinazuki got back home at 9 p.m.
After that, her mother and
her mother's boyfriend beat her.
Before 11 p.m., she disappeared
from the shed they'd locked her in.
At 12:30 a.m., Hinazuki's mom called mine.
The culprit murdered Hinazuki
before sunrise on the 3rd.
Not only have Hinazuki's actions
and ours changed a lot this time,
but so have Hinazuki's mom's,
and the killer's.
Everything from now on is uncharted territory.
This is Yashiro Gaku.
I'm a teacher at Mikoto Elementary School.
Yes, please.
Don't tell Kazu or Osamu about this.
And, uh, sorry for dragging you into this, Hiromi.
I'm just glad you asked me for help, no matter how.
And even if I'd gone home,
I would've been all by myself until 8 p.m.
Sorry for cooping you up in here, too, Kayo.
Don't be. I've never had this much fun before.
I'm glad I mustered up the courage to come.
I'm gonna drop by your place tomorrow morning.
And leave her mom with no choice
but to call the cops, huh?
Yeah.
Listen, I more or less get the gist of it,
but who's gonna handle the fallout?
Don't worry. I'll take full responsibility.
Are you stupid?
If we say it was my idea,
and you guys only helped me out...
we all get away scot-free, right?
There, I win.
She's right.
I never even considered that angle.
On the way home, Kenya said,
"I bet you hadn't thought of that."
When I told him I hadn't, he added...
"In my eyes, that's what heroes are like."
Is that Satoru?